<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>data processing on Selena Tabbara</title>
    <link>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/tags/data-processing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in data processing on Selena Tabbara</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 11:25:05 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/tags/data-processing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Privacy for Activity Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/project/final-year-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/project/final-year-project/</guid>
      <description>With the advance of smartphones, wearables devices, and other Internet of Things devices, there is a variety of sensors that are generating time-series measurements of your daily activity. These sensors allow the emergence of new services that are beneficial to several areas including health monitoring, safety, and productivity. While cameras, microphones, and the location are preserved as privacy-sensitive, the privacy implication of activity recognition sensors is still underestimated. In fact, the detailed time-series user data shared with untrusted third parties could be used to infer private and sensitive information user information (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinical Decision Support System for COVID-19 patients management</title>
      <link>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/project/project-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/project/project-6/</guid>
      <description>Everybody has head about COVID The first case of COVID-19 was detected in Wuhan, China, on December 31st, 2019. Soon after, the WHO has characterized this viral disease as a global pandemic. Many governments have imposed a lockdown to protect the NHS from being overwhelmed and limit the spread of the disease. Since then, the COVID-19 has seriously impacted businesses and the economy. It also has been had serious implications for people&amp;rsquo;s livelihoods and health.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
