<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Experience on Selena Tabbara</title>
    <link>https://selenatabbara.com/experience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Experience on Selena Tabbara</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://selenatabbara.com/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Research in Reinforcement Learning at Imperial College London</title>
      <link>https://selenatabbara.com/experience/urop-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://selenatabbara.com/experience/urop-2020/</guid>
      <description>The UROP is still in progress and the page will be updated!
I am working as part of Undergraduate Research Opportunities Program (UROP) at the Information Processing and Communications Lab in Imperial College London. I have worked on privacy aware data sharing for the new generation electricity supply network, using Reinforcement Learning.
In the new generation electricity supply networks, smart meters play a key role in recording the electricity consumption of a household and report it to the utility provider in real time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Creator Intern at ARM</title>
      <link>https://selenatabbara.com/experience/internship-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://selenatabbara.com/experience/internship-2019/</guid>
      <description>During my 12 weeks internship, I was a content creator intern in the Arm University Program. I worked on revamping one of the educational kits, Rapid Embedded Design and Programming Online Course, under the supervision of my line manager.
The Rapid Embedded Design and Programming Online Course is a 10/14 weeks university course which aims to help the student develop their skills of using high level programming tools and languages to rapidly design and program Arm-based embedded systems and prototype them for various applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work Shadowing Programs Learning About Warehouse Management at MORECO</title>
      <link>https://selenatabbara.com/experience/internship-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://selenatabbara.com/experience/internship-2018/</guid>
      <description>link website - talk about what I learned - also refrigerating systems &amp;hellip;..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intensive Training Program at Tabbara Electro-Mechanics</title>
      <link>https://selenatabbara.com/experience/internship-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://selenatabbara.com/experience/internship-2017/</guid>
      <description>1 month intensive training program in which I have learned about the logistics behind the electro-mechanics distribution company and gained insights on major electrical components used in control and power electronic
link to website - what is the company what did it do
  Illustration from Victor Hugo et son temps (1881)   Link to GitHub repository</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>