<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Experience on Selena Tabbara</title>
    <link>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/experience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Experience on Selena Tabbara</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Preserving Machine Learning Research at Imperial College London</title>
      <link>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/experience/urop-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/experience/urop-2020/</guid>
      <description>I am working as part of Undergraduate Research Opportunities Program (UROP) at the Information Processing and Communications Lab at Imperial College London.
Privacy Aware Sharing in Smart Grids In the new generation electricity supply networks, smart meters play a key role in recording the electricity consumption of a household by reporting it to the utility provider in real time. However, this real-time information also carries sensitive personal information about the user&amp;rsquo;s activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Creator Intern at ARM</title>
      <link>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/experience/internship-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/experience/internship-2019/</guid>
      <description>During my 12 weeks internship, I was a content creator intern in the Arm University Program. I worked on revamping one of the educational kits, Rapid Embedded Design and Programming Online Course, under the supervision of my line manager.
The Rapid Embedded Design and Programming Online Course is a 10/14 weeks university course which aims to help the student develop their skills of using high level programming tools and languages to rapidly design and program Arm-based embedded systems and prototype them for various applications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>