<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Selena Tabbara</title>
    <link>http://selenatabbara.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Selena Tabbara</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://selenatabbara.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinical Decision Support System for COVID-19 patients management</title>
      <link>http://selenatabbara.github.io/post/project-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://selenatabbara.github.io/post/project-6/</guid>
      <description>EPIC IMPOC is a clinical decision support system used in the NHS to improve the management of infectious diseases by facilitating data collection, infection diagnostics and antimicrobial therapy advice at the point of care.
In the midst of the SARS-CoV-2 outbreak, we implemented a new module in EPIC IMPOC (Enhanced, Personalized and Integrated Care for Infection Management at the Point of Care), specifically to provide aid to clinicians to diagnose COVID-19 patients and treat them by retrieving similar cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HLP</title>
      <link>http://selenatabbara.github.io/post/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://selenatabbara.github.io/post/project-5/</guid>
      <description>F# project description - what we have managed to achieve check the first report deliverable + GitHUb</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EE1 Rover Group Project</title>
      <link>http://selenatabbara.github.io/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://selenatabbara.github.io/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>PICTURE video maybe youtube what I have done Worked on the implementation of the sensors, the mobile application design, the user interface, the intelligent unit, the maneuverability of the Rover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Smart monitor</title>
      <link>http://selenatabbara.github.io/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://selenatabbara.github.io/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>link to our website get information from There iot protocols Embeddedc++ Deep NN Frequency to picture to - 5s interval</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Mind Solver using Genetic Algorithm </title>
      <link>http://selenatabbara.github.io/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://selenatabbara.github.io/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>check my report maybe link it ? cover letter used c++ ressources used maybe</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edge Makers Inc., Riyada - Innovation camp</title>
      <link>http://selenatabbara.github.io/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://selenatabbara.github.io/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>descriptionInnovation camp around solving an environmental problem related to waste (2 weeks) Developed a business scheme as well as a mobile app to solve the problem, using JAVA as a computer language. Gave a speech to the minister of communication and a representative of the prime minister at the Government Palace. Participated in a TV interview. Gained leadership, innovation and entrepreneurship skills. maybe link to TV interview picture of me giving a speech</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>