<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>embedded electronics on Selena Tabbara</title>
    <link>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/tags/embedded-electronics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in embedded electronics on Selena Tabbara</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 11:14:48 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/tags/embedded-electronics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Baby monitor</title>
      <link>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>We have implemented a smart baby monitor that record the regularly the temperature of a baby and save it on online database. It uses machine learning to check if the baby is crying or not.
An android user friendly mobile application has been made so that the parents can receiver notification and check on the baby&amp;rsquo;s temperature and its history using Java as a programming language.   Screenshot of the mobile application&amp;#39;s main view   The ARM microcontroller is programmed to collect the read the data from the sensor using I2C protocol and C++ as a programming language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Creator Intern at ARM</title>
      <link>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/experience/internship-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/experience/internship-2019/</guid>
      <description>During my 12 weeks internship, I was a content creator intern in the Arm University Program. I worked on revamping one of the educational kits, Rapid Embedded Design and Programming Online Course, under the supervision of my line manager.
The Rapid Embedded Design and Programming Online Course is a 10/14 weeks university course which aims to help the student develop their skills of using high level programming tools and languages to rapidly design and program Arm-based embedded systems and prototype them for various applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EE1 Rover Group Project</title>
      <link>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://selenatabbara.github.io/portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>The aim of this project is to implement a remotely-controlled rover that can explore a hazardous store room and identify unusual material that would emit a combination of different signals (infrared and radio signals) using C++ as a computer language and Arduino IDE as a development tool.
As part of the project I have worked on the implementation of the sensors, the mobile application design, the user interface, the intelligent unit, the maneuverability of the rover.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>